U.S. Agency for International Development Records, Programs, and Itineraries 5384
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI. Training Manuals
  - Using Job Instruction Training (Box 4, Folder 23)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 8
  - Union Job Relations Training Manual (Box 4, Folder 23)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 9
  - Job Relations Training Case Studies (Box 4, Folder 23)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 10
  - Training Course in Material Handling (Box 4, Folder 23)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 11
  - Discussion Leadership: Suggestions on the Conduct of Small Group Discussions (Box 4, Folder 23)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 12
  - The Supervisory Six (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 13
  - New Foreman Training Plan (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 14
  - Selection and Training of New Foremen (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 15
  - Power Plant Training Course: Steam Accessories (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 16
  - General Operating Rules for Power Boilers (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 17
  - Plant Fire Brigade Training (Box 4, Folder 24)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 18
  - Industrial First Aid Training (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 19
  - Communications in Business and Industry (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 20
  - Conference Leadership Training (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 21
  - Economics Training (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 22
  - Effective Job Organization, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 23
  - Management Development Programs for Executives and Supervisors and Manufacturing Division, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 24
  - Fundamentals of Management: Basic Supervisory Training, Training in Human Relations, Leadership Training, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 25
  - Maintenance Training Program, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 26
  - Problems in Business Management: Nature and Scope of Management Responsibilities (Box 4, Folder 26)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 27
  - Problems in Business Management: Organization (Box 4, Folder 26)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 28
  - Problems in Business Management: Human Relations (Box 4, Folder 26)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 29
  - Problems in Business Management: Management Training (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 30
  - Problems in Business Management: Incentive Plans (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 31
  - Problems in Business Management: Manufacturing Costs (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 32
  - Problems in Business Management: Production Planning (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 33
  - Problems in Business Management (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 34
  - Problems in Business Management: Costs and Budgets (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 35
  - Problems in Business Management: Business Leadership (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 36
  - Industrial Training Sound Films (Box 4, Folder 27)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 38
  - Management and Supervisory Training Program, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 39
  - Economics Training: Charts (Box 4, Folder 28)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 40
  - Operating a Fork Truck (Box 4, Folder 28)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 41
  - Waste Reduction, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 42
  - Lubrication Fundamentals and Practices, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 43
  - Lubrication Fundamentals and Practices, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 44
  - Personnel Management, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 45
  - Machinery Manufacturing Cost Accounting (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 46
  - The Responsibility of the Training Supervisor (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 47
  - Induction Training (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 48
  - Production Training (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 49
  - Preparation of Training Course Outlines (Box 4, Folder 29)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 50
  - Departmental Personnel Procedures, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 51
  - How to Select New Supervisors, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 52
  - Techniques of Day-to-Day Supervisor: Performance Levels Depend on Quality of Supervision, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 53
  - Selecting Management Personnel, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 54
  - Memo and Report Writing, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 55
  - Public Relations Training, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 56
  - Industrial Training Methods (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 57
  - Training Course in Cost Accounting (Box 4, Folder 30)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 59
  - Cost Control Accounting (Box 4, Folder 31)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 60
  - Training Course in Marketing (Box 4, Folder 31)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 61
  - Metal-Working Industry Training Manual (Box 4, Folder 31)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 62
  - Department Store Merchandising (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 63
  - Record-Keeping Forms for the Handcrafter, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 64
  - Retail Selling (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 65
  - Quality Control (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 66
  - Training TWI Trainers Top Management Seminars Starting a Management Association, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 67
  - Production Management Methods in a Small Shop (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 68
  - Management's Responsibility for Supervision (Box 4, Folder 32)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 69
  - Office Training (Box 4, Folder 33)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 70
  - Wage Incentives, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 71
  - Supervisory Training Through Individual Coaching, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 72
  - Industrial Safety leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 73
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide (Box 5, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Technical Bulletin No. 74
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide (Box 5, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 75
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 76
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 77
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 78
  - Industrial Safety Guide, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 79
  - Industrial Safety Leader's Guide, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 80
  - Purchasing (Supervisory Trainee Program) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 81
  - Production Planning and Control, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 82
  - Manufacturing and Manufacturing Engineer, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 83
  - Job Analysis, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 84
  - Plant Maintenance and Housekeeping, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 85
  - Paperwork Simplification, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 86
  - Job Evaluation Operating Procedures, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No. 87
  - The Art of Motivating People, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.88
  - Production Scheduling and Control, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.89
  - Time and Motion Study, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.90
  - Management Primer: Management and Productivity, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.91
  - Management Primer: Enterprise Organization, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.92
  - Management Primer: Human Relations in Management, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.93
  - Management Primer: Personnel Administration, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.94
  - Management Primer: Control and Supervision, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.95
  - Management Primer: Records and Reports, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.96
  - Management Primer: Production Management, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Training Manual No. 97
  - Management Primer: Procurement and Inventory, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Training Manual No. 98
  - Management Primer: Financial Management, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.99
  - Management Primer: Distribution and Sales, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.100
  - Management Primer: Research and Public Relations, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.101
  - Management Primer: Management Glossary, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.102
  - Sales Promotion Methods, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.103
  - Distribution Methods, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.104
  - Wholesale Merchandising, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.105
  - A Basic Course in Work Study, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.106
  - Work Simplification for Increased Productivity, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 107
  - Foreman Training Course (Box 5, Folder 8)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.108
  - Sales Training and Distribution, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.109
  - Executive's Role in an Organization, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.110
  - Time Study Practice and Procedure, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Training Manual No. 111
  - A Suggestion System, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.112
  - A Suggestion System, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 112
  - Science of Human Relations, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.113
  - Taking Annual Inventory, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.114
  - Fire Control Training, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Training Manual No. 115
  - Basic Course in Work Sampling, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.116
  - Marketing Research, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.117
  - Wood Furniture Industry, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.118
  - Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.119
  - Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.120
  - Leather Chemistry for Foremen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.121
  - Management and Supervision of a Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.122
  - Management and Supervision of Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.123
  - Management and Supervision of a Sales Force, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.124
  - Personnel Management: Job Analysis, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.125
  - Personnel Management: Selection and Placement of Personnel, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.126
  - Personnel Management: Job Evaluation, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.127
  - Personnel Management: Wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.128
  - Personnel Management: Wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.129
  - Personnel Management: wage and Salary Administration, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.130
  - Personnel Management: Personnel Records and Statistics, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.131
  - Advertising Principles and Problems, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.132
  - Line-Staff Relationships, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 134
  - Performance Discussions, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 135
  - Foundry Supervisory Training: Molding and Core Sands, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.136
  - Foundry Supervisory Training: Cupola Design and Operation, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.137
  - Foundry Supervisory Training: General Molding Practice, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    International Cooperation Administration; Training Manual No.138
  - Supervisory Safety Training (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Agency for International Development; Training Manual No.139
  - Basic Course in Production Planning and Control, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 141
  - The Art of Making Molds, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 142
  - Economics of Industrial Development, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 143
  - Economic Development Case Problems, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Department of State, Agency for International Development; Training Manual No. 144